Where the legend ends and the man begins.
MacArthur is a drama, history, war film directed by Joseph Sargent.
The film portrays MacArthur's life from 1942, before the Battle of Bataan, to 1952, when he was removed from his Korean
War command by President Truman for insubordination, and is recounted in flashback as he visits West Point.
Douglas MacArthur, played by Gregory Peck.
Lt. Gen. Richard K. Sutherland, played by Ivan Bonar.
Gen. George C. Marshall, played by Ward Costello.
Colonel Sidney Huff, played by Nicolas Coster.
Jean MacArthur, played by Marj Dusay.
President Harry S. Truman, played by Ed Flanders.
MacArthur is a 1977 American biographical war film directed by Joseph Sargent and starring
Gregory Peck in the eponymous role as American General of the Army Douglas MacArthur.
The film explores themes of world war ii, korean war
(1950-53), biography, pacific war, west point.
The tone is emotional.